<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HealthAndFitnessApp</string>

    <string name="mainText1">Welcome,  </string>

    <string name="mainText2">. \nWhat do you want to do today?</string>

    <string name="calCountUnit">Daily amount in kg</string>

    <string name="instructions">
        Please watch the video linked below, detailing the workout\n
        \nFollow the instructions provided in the video and complete the workout.\n
        \nAfter completing the workout, self evaluate yourself on number of reps, speed, form, etc.\n
        \nAccording to your self evaluation, press 1 of the 3 buttons provided below to record your progress.\n

    </string>

    <string-array name="healthTips">
        <item>1. Do not drink sugar calories: Sugary drinks are among the most fattening items you can put into your body.</item>
        <item>2. Eat nuts : Despite being high in fat, nuts are incredibly nutritious and healthy, and help fight heart disease.</item>
        <item>3. Do not fear coffee : It is high in antioxidants, and studies have linked it to longevity.</item>
        <item>4. Get enough sleep : Sleep deprivation is one of the strongest individual risk factors for weight gain and obesity.</item>
        <item>5. Take probiotics and fibre : The bacteria in your gut are incredibly important for overall health.</item>
        <item>6. Drink some water: Drinking enough water can boost metabolism.</item>
        <item>7. Don’t overcook your meat : Overcooking meat can lead to the formation of cancerogenic substances.</item>
        <item>8. Avoid bright lights before sleep: Use warm light and filter glasses to block blue light and improve sleep quality.</item>
        <item>9. Eat enough protein : Protein is vital for optimal health and is particularly important for weight loss.</item>
        <item>10. Do some cardio : Cardio is one of the best things you can do for your mental and physical health.</item>
        <item>11. Use extra virgin olive oil : It is one of the healthiest vegetable oils, loaded with anti inflammatory agents</item>
        <item>12. Do not eat refined carbs : They are highly processed, low in nutrients, and can harm your health when eaten in excess.</item>
        <item>13. Lift heavy things : Lifting weights strengthens your muscles and body composition. It also leads to improvements in metabolism.</item>
        <item>14. Avoid processed junk food. All your exercise will go to waste</item>
        <!--<item>4. Do not drink sugar calories. NO, diet coke does not count!</item>
        <item> Get enough sleep; Exercise cannot replace that</item>
        <item>2. Drink plenty of water. All that sweat comes from somewhere, right!</item>
        -->
        <item>15. Eat vegetables and fruits. They also are the best bang for the buck and good for the environment too</item>
        <item>16. Do not Smoke. Duh!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="exercises">
        <item>Chest Workout</item>
        <item>Shoulder Workout</item>
        <item>Back Workout</item>
        <item>Biceps Workout</item>
        <item>Triceps Workout</item>
        <item>Legs Workout</item>
        <item>Abs Workout</item>
        <item>Cardio</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="links">
        <item>https://youtu.be/UU_UnZjtG74</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/mbkIELD3AqM</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/ct9OFwNUtdQ</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/kYUMGjubpQg</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/W2PleUxEVuw</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/pN84zT_eKCQ</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/8e8wEwnFuYo</item>
        <item>https://youtu.be/QdAX3MyqV38</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>